United Overseas Bank Bhd is collaborating
with Prudential Assurance Malaysia Berhad
to provide customers with a suite of insurance
solutions digitally through a new virtual
face-to-face feature on Pulse1, the insurer’s
all-in-one health and wellness app.
It said UOB Malaysia was the first bank in
Southeast Asia to use the VF2F feature, enabling
its customers to manage their insurance needs
digitally and conveniently, particularly important
during the ongoing pandemic.
“The VF2F feature also enables the bank’s
customers to submit the necessary documentation
and forms electronically, eliminating the
need to fill in a physical questionnaire.
“As the entire process, from receiving financial
guidance to applying for and confirming their
insurance coverage is conducted on the app,
customers can fulfil their protection and
wealth planning needs in a simpler, smarter
and swifter manner without visiting a branch,”
it said in a joint statement.
UOB Malaysia managing director and country
head of personal financial services Ronnie
Lim said the collaboration with PAMB demonstrated
the bank’s commitment to providing customers
with progressive and convenient solutions
that are relevant to their lifestyle needs
and preferences and in the manner they prefer.
“The introduction of the VF2F feature to
offer customers protection solutions is timely
given the latest surge in Covid-19 cases.
“With more consumers using smartphones to
manage their financial needs, we hope that
one in every two customers will benefit from
this new feature and sign up for the protection
or wealth solutions that we offer together
with PAMB,” Lim said.
PAMB senior director, partnerships distribution
Lee Ee Hui said the pandemic had elevated
the awareness of insurance protection and
the critical need to be financially protected.
“With this partnership, we are able to offer
UOB Malaysia’s customers a secure end to-end
service anytime, anywhere through our AI-powered
health app, Pulse,” he said.